- 把你的手机给我  - 够了
- Give me your phone. - That's it.
Debbie Fogle 你被逮捕了
Debbie Fogle, you are under arrest.
你说什么 哦我的天
What? Oh, my God.
你不是真的黑警吗
Are you not really dirty?
不是 而且我要没收你的枪
No. And I'll be taking that gun.
嗨呀
Hi-ya!
看起来女子健身房和可卡因
Okay so the women's gym and the cocaine
让Debbie有了超能力
have given Debbie super powers.
酷 酷 酷 酷 酷 酷 酷 酷 酷
Cool. Cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool.
你正在犯大错 Debbie
You're making a big mistake, Debbie.
这样是行不通的
This isn't gonna work.
我真不会看人
I'm such a terrible judge of character,
我看错了Rosa
who was wrong about Rosa,
Jared Fogle 美国赛百味三明治前代言人 后被指控犯性侵罪还没看出表亲Jared给我的所有暗示
and missed all the signs with my cousin Jared.
- 给赛百味代言的那货  - 我脑子有毛病吧
- The sandwich guy. - What is wrong with me?
没事 你会这样难受
Nothing, you're just coming down
只是因为之前吸的那么多可卡因
from the many handfuls of coke you did.